Finding Aid for Thomas L. Hankinson papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs
  - Negatives (Staff use only-Glass)
    - August 1913-June 1919 (Box 8)
      - 1918
        - August 26, Rocky Island at Car Pond (Box 8)
        - August, Hemlock Mt. Palisades Interstate Park (Box 8)
        - August, Cedar Pond (Box 8)
        - September 29, Stn. 11 and 7. Head of campus stream bed (Box 8)
        - October 6, Stn-130. Wrightville Pond (Box 8)
        - October 13, Stn. 90. Embarrass Valley from upland woods SE of Watermalos [?] showing tree covered river bank in background, woods in foreground (Box 8)
        - October, Pool north of Wrightville (Box 8)
      - 1919
        - April 6, Station 23 (near). Woods NE of Stn.23 (Box 8)
        - April 6, Station 21. Falls barrier for fish (18-20 in. high) (Box 8)
        - April 6, Station 23. Blue racer [snake] (Box 8)
        - April 6, Station 21 looking NW from hill at east end of station (Box 8)
        - April 7, Station 4, Normal School forest. Milk snake collected April 6, 1919 (Box 8)
        - April 12, Station 310. Barker's Woods looking NW across wheat field (Box 8)
        - April, Bufo americanus in lab [frog] (Box 8)
        - April, Acris gryllus [frog] in lab (Box 8)
        - April, Washed ravine north of Wrightville (Box 8)
        - April, "Lovers' Lane" Road (Box 8)
        - April, Pool SW of Wrightville on "Lovers' Lane" Road (Box 8)
        - May 2, Station 309. Headwaters of Cossil Creek. Looking northerly. Net on bank near Bolissum negrum [?] nest (Box 8)
        - May 2, Station 310. Baker's Woods. Part of west aide (Box 8)
        - May 2, Station 310. Baker's Woods. North part looking north (Box 8)
          (Note: From this point through June 7, 1919 and then again on August 27, 1919 photos were made in and around the Warren Forest Preserve, Berrien Co., Michigan. From June 21, 1919 to August 23, 1919 photos were made in and around Palisades Interstate Park, New York.)
        - June 1, Warren Woods looking south (east portion). Warren Forest Preserve. (1) (Box 8)
        - June 1, Warren Woods looking south (west portion). (2) (Box 8)
          (Note: to be paired with the preceding, this to right.)
        - June 1, Warren Woods, looking east from Rev. Helming's. (5) (Box 8)
        - June 2, Station 50. Galien River, looking downstream, Warren Forest Preserve (Box 8)
        - June 2, Station 45. Galien River, looking south, downstream (Box 8)
        - June 2, Station 30. Galien River, looking upstream, showing sand bank with dip net landing. Hybopsis[?] kentuckiensis nest slightly shown at x-x. Others in vicinity. See June 2 and 3 notes. (9) (Box 8)
        - June 2, Stn. 30. Galien River looking downstream in thick woods. (10) (Box 8)
        - June 2, Swamp in Warren Woods. (12) (Box 8)
        - June 3, Chrysemys laying eggs in burrow, undisturbed. Bank of Galien River. (14) (Box 8)
        - June 3, Nesting habitat of Chrysemys. Bank of Galien River. Note book at nest. (16) (Box 8)
        - June 5, Large sand dune and Lake Michigan about 3 miles north of Sawyer, Berrien Co. (18) (Box 8)
        - June 5, Large sand dune along Lake Michigan about 3 miles north of Sawyer. Same dune as in photo 18 but looking away from lake. (19) (Box 8)
        - June 5, Sand blowout 1/4 mile or so long about 3 miles north of Sawyer, Mich., on Lake Michigan. (20) (Box 8)
        - June 5, Plants holding sand. Sand dunes about 3 miles north of Sawyer. (21) (Box 8)
        - June 5, Blowout on Lake Michigan about 3 miles north of Sawyer, looking toward lake. (22) (Box 8)
        - June 7, Near Station 30. Warren Woods and lane along river. (29) (Box 8)
        - June 7, Near Stn. 30. Warren Woods, low portion. (31) (Box 8)
        - June 7, Galien River, near station 25. East part of woods downstream. (33) (Box 8)
        - June 7, Swam-p near Station 25 in Warren Woods (Box 8)
        - June 21, Little Long Pond from side of Tom Jones Mt. looking NW. Palisades Interstate Park, N.Y. (Box 8)
        - June 23, Bullfrog on bank of S. Kahnawake [?] Lake, N.Y. (Box 8)
        - June 25, Cedar Pond Dam (Box 8)
        - June 29, Little Long Pond and part of region west of it, looking easterly (Box 8)
        - June 29, Little Long Pond and W. Kahnawake Lake from Tom Jones Hill (Box 8)
        - June 30, Popolopen [?] Creek about 1/4 mile upstream from Old Furnace, N.Y. (Box 8)
    - July 1919-June 1931 (Box 9)
      - 1919
        - July 3, Boys bathing at Car Pond. Palisade Park (Box 9)
        - July 11, Investigating party, guest house camp, Palisade Park (Box 9)
        - July 27, Dr. Harris, son and nephew, Warner, N.Y. (Box 9)
        - July 27, Dr. Harris and relatives, Warner, N.Y. (Box 9)
        - July 27, Dr. Harris, family and relatives, Warner, N.Y. (Box 9)
        - August 20, Mt. Haystack from Mt. Marcy, N.Y., looking easterly (Box 9)
        - August 21, Valley SE of Mt. Marcy, from side of Mt. Marcy (Box 9)
        - August 23, Camp at Mt. Marcy showing mountain top (Box 9)
        - August 27, Galien River from bridge about 1 1/4 miles below, SW of Warren Forest Preserve. (35) (Box 9)
        - August 27, Galien River looking upstream about 1 mile below or SW of Warren Forest, a shallow, sandy portion of stream. (36) (Box 9)
        - August 27, Galien River looking downstream about 1 mile below, SW of Warren Forest. (37) (Box 9)
        - August 27, Galien River looking upstream about 2 miles NE of New Buffalo, Mich., from large main road bridge. (40) (Box 9)
        - October 19, West Tile Factory Pond, Charleston, Ill, with E. N. Transeau (Box 9)
      - 1921
        - April 8, Breeding stream of Corusum sucker [?], Catosturus cammerssini [?]. Fish seen spawning. See Oneida Lake Coll. 4206 A (Box 9)
      - 1925
        (Note: From this point through 1934 photos were made in and, around Ypsilanti, Michigan and other localities as indicated. Hankinson was teaching at the State Normal College at Ypsilanti (later Eastern Michigan University).)
        - January 24, Eclipse of sun (Box 9)
        - January 24, Eclipse of sun (Box 9)
        - March 15, Nuthatch at feeding station (Box 9)
        - June 19, Nest of Great Blue Heron, woods north of Geddes, Mich. (Box 9)
        - June 19, Nesting habitat of Great Blue Heron, woods north of Geddes, Mich. (Box 9)
        - July, Night blooming cereus, Mich. State Normal College greenhouse (Box 9)
        - December 23, House sparrow at suet, 96 Oakwood Ave., Ypsilanti (Box 9)
        - December 23, Bobwhites in yard, 96 Oakwood Ave., Ypsilanti (Box 9)
        - December 25, Bobwhites and squirrel in yard, 96 Oakwood Ave. (Box 9)
      - 1926
        - January, Bobwhites in yard. (19262) (Box 9)
        - May 1, Brook lampreys in nest. Enterphum[?] appendix. Fleming Creek.(192616) (Box 9)
        - June 11, Nest of migrant Shrike. Just southeast of Ypsilanti on the Belleville Road. (2646) (Box 9)
        - June 27, Pittsfield Ponds 5-6 miles west of Ypsilanti. (272) (Box 9)
        - November 14, Blue Jay at feeding station. 96 Oakwood Ave. (Box 9)
        - December 12, Blue Jay at feeding station. 96 Oakwood Ave. (Box 9)
        - December 12, Blue Jay at feeding station (Box 9)
      - 1927
        - May 28, Cattail marsh, nesting habitat of redwing blackbirds, Florida gallimile [?], bronzed [?] grackle. Pittsfield Ponds. (275) (Box 9)
        - May 28, Pittsfield Ponds just east of woods looking northerly. (272) (Box 9)
        - Ma7), 28, Nest of Florida Gallimile, Washtenaw Co. (2730) (Box 9)
        - May 28, Nest, of Florida Gallimile, Washtenaw Co. (2737) (Box 9)
      - 1928
        - June 28, Young fish 5 mm. long, station 114-115 off Maumee Bay, Lake Erie. (3078) (Box 9)
      - 1929
        - June 8, Young chipping sparrow in bush by science building (Box 9)
        - June 8, Young brown thrashers in nest on ground, Normal College Campus (Box 9)
        - June 8, Young brown thrashers in nest in circle, with nesting habitat of brown thrashers (Box 9)
        - June 14, Night herons nests. Rawsonville (Box 9)
        - June 14, Night herons nests with young (Box 9)
        - Summer, Nest and young of black crowned night herons, Rawsonville (Box 9)
        - July, Edison Lake, showing tree tops of flooded trees where black-crowned night herons nested [?] (Box 9)
        - July 4, Woods along Fleming Creek west of gravel pit (Box 9)
        - July 4, Frog Pond at gravel pit, north of Geddes, Mich. (Box 9)
        - July 4, Region west of Geddes Gravel Pit (Box 9)
        - July 13, Wamplers Lake from Tower [?] (Box 9)
        - July 13, Looking westerly [?] from Gray Tower, Lenawee Co. (Box 9)
      - 1930
        - April, Great blue heron. T.S., Wiard's Woods (Box 9)
        - May 4, Rawsonville Heronry (Box 9)
        - May 4, Rawsonville Heronry. Night herons in background (Box 9)
        - May 4, Rawsonville Heronry. Night herons in tree (Box 9)
        - May 4, Rawsonville Heronry. Night herons in nest (Box 9)
        - May 4, Night herons at Rawsonville Heronry (Box 9)
        - May 14, Double nest of song sparrow, Saline, Mich. (Box 9)
        - May 14, Double nest of song sparrow, Saline, Mich. (Box 9)
        - May 14, Interior of Cady's Woods (Box 9)
        - May 14, Tamarack Swamp, west margin of Cady's Swamp (Box 9)
        - May 14, Roberts Pond, looking northerly from Saline Road (Box 9)
        - May 30, Three negatives formerly in one jacket labeled: "Breeding habitat of [7 species, illegible] May 8-23, 1930. Shallows above ripples shown in foreground. Photo taken May 30, 1930. Up stream at Tourist Camp, Saline River, Saline, Mich." Negatives marked:
          - "Pool above ripples. Down stream, May 30, 1930" (Box 9)
          - " May 30, 1930. Up stream" (Box 9)
          - " May 30, 1930. Down stream" (Box 9)
        - June, Rawsonville Heronry (Box 9)
        - June 1, Paint Creek. Coll.300601. Made lure [?]. Looking upstream. Slaughter's place about 3 miles south of Ypsilanti (Box 9)
        - June 4, Saline River habitat of nesting fish. Bank with swallows' nests (Box 9)
        - July 15, Notropis atherimadis (?) [question mark his]. Very young, near 4 mm. Meter net collected [?], Lake Erie. (Box 9)
        - July 29, Perca flauseum. Hatchery fish. (5) (Box 9)
        - August 2[?] Notropis atherimadis(?). Same fish as No-7 (Box 9)
        - August 2[?], Perca flauseum (286-127B). (August 2-No.5) (Box 9)
        - August 2[?], Perca flauseum Posttana [?]. (Coll. 286-127B) (Box 9)
        - August 2[?], Fish. Posterior ends 6.5-7 cm. C?I. (Coll. 287-163B). (3051) (Box 9)
        - August 2[?], Notropis atherimadia photomicrograph [?]. Two specimens showing heads. Same fish as 9. (3055) (Box 9)
        - August 2[?], Perca flauseum Posttarea photomicrograph [?]. Meter net collection [?]. (3056) (Box 9)
        - August 6, Young fish showing gill area (Box 9)
        - August 6, Coll. 283-163F, 8 mm. long each (Box 9)
        - August 6, Coll. 283-163F, 8 mm. long each [tails] (Box 9)
        - August 6, Coll. 287-163F fish, 8 mm. long (Box 9)
        - August 6, Coll. 287-163F, fish 8 mm. long (Box 9)
        - August 7, Perca flauseum. Hatching fish, 5mm. long. (3074) (Box 9)
        - August 15, Jaws of Stigastidian [?] canadense Posttaria. Coll.286-107C, June 14, 1928. (3052) (Box 9)
        - August 15[?], Head, gums, teeth, Perca flauseum, Coll. 2806-72A. (3053) (Box 9)
        - August 15[?], Lepebema (?) [question mark his]. Coll. 286-153A. Fish 5 mm. Collected June 28, 1928 off Maumee Bay, Lake Erie. (3054) (Box 9)
        - August 15[?] Teeth of Stryastidin [?] canadense. (3057) (Box 9)
        - August 15[?], Teeth of Stryastidin vitrium. (No. 2806-59B). Meter net collection[?] (Box 9)
        - August 15[?], Teeth of Stryastidin. (2806-59B). Fish about 12 mm. (Box 9)
        - August 15[?], Hylopsis storerianis [?]. (297-461). Fish about 6 mm. Identified by Mrs. C. E. Fish. (306-0) (Box 9)
        - August 15[?], Percina esprades [?]. No.297-462. Fish about 7 mm. (Box 9)
        - August 15[?], Stryastidium and Perca. Coll. 2806-59B. 11 and 12 mm. (3062) (Box 9)
        - Sent. 3, Maxistoma, anterior part. Fish 8 mm. long. Meter net coil. (-Ro66 No.1) (Box 9)
        - September 3, Maxistoma[?]. Meter net Coll., Lake Erie, Fish 8 mm. long (3065-No.2) (Box 9)
        - September 3, Perca flauseum. Jaws to show teeth. Fish c.30 mm. long. Meter net Coll., 286-100A. (No.3) (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Notrapis atherimadis [?] Posttaria [?], 5.5 mm. Coll. 207-166B (2063-No.5) (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Perca flauseum. No.2806-50. Hu[?]l tails of two fish 8 and 9 mm. (3064-No.3) (Box 9)
        - September 3, Perca flauseum. Meter net coil. 286-100A. Fish 13 mm. Same as 3. 4. (No.5) (Box 9)
        - September 3, Perca flauseum, teeth with maxillary and lower jaws, 10 mm. long. No.286-270A (3067-No.6) (Box 9)
        - September 3, Perca flauseum. Meter net coll. 286-100A. Fish 13 mm., same as No-3 (3068-No.4) (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Perca flauseum[?], Clodocerans[?] in stomach. Coll. 2806-60 (3069-slide 7) (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Notrapis atherimadis. Myomeris[?], parts of two pigment bodies. Coll.828-208A. (3070-slide 3) (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Notrapis atherimadis showing air bladder. Coll-300754. Fish 10 mm. long (3071-No.7) (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Cottus bairdis larva. Anterior end. 7 mm. 2805-45D. (3072) (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Cottus bairdis. Posterior end. 7 mm. 2805-45D. (3073) (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Stryastidium and Perca. Fish 11 and 12 mm. Coll. 2806-59B (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Perca flauseum. 2806-72A (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Perca flauseum. 2806-84 (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Jaws of Perca flauseum Posttaria. 2806-72A (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Jaws of Perca flauseum Posttaria. 2806-87B. Collected 6-14-28 (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Perca flauseum showing teeth. 2806-34 (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Perca flauseum. Central[?] portion. 2306-84A. See anterior Portion (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Perca flauseum. Tails showing deflected notachord[?]. (8) (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Perca flauseum. Tails showing straight notachords[?]. (11) (Box 9)
        - September 3[?], Perca flauseum. Tails showing degree of notachord[?] deflertion. About 10 mm. No.2806-62A (Box 9)
        - November, Rough-legged hawk with Arrms[?]. No.19301 (Box 9)
      - 1931
        - February 23, Apple tree with frozen front [?]. Attractive to 50-100 Cedar Waxwings (Box 9)
        - February 26, East Ilix Bay looking easterly (Box 9)
        - March 3, Burning over a meadow at Ilix Bay, 2 miles east [west?] of Normal College, Ypsilanti (Box 9)
        - March 3, Ilix Bay looking east toward the East Bay. Showing muskrat trail (see hat on trail) (Box 9)
        - March 9, Nuthatch at feeding station. 96 Oakwood Ave., Ypsilanti (Box 9)
        - March 22, Valley of Saline River (Box 9)
        - April, Grass nest. Willow Run, Wayne Co. (Box 9)
        - April, Heronry in Wiard's Woods, heron about nests (Box 9)
        - April, Blue herons at nests, Wiard's Woods (Box 9)
        - April, Great Blue herons at nests, Wiard's Woods (Box 9)
        - April, Fallen nest of great blue heron (Box 9)
        - April, Nest and eggs of Killdeer. College campus (Box 9)
        - April, Edison Lake, looking west from bluff showing Rawsonville from bluff and also remnants of dead woods where black crowned night herons nested in 1929-30 (Box 9)
        - April, Eggs of Perca flauseum. Aquarium at Ann Arbor (Box 9)
        - April, Great Blue Heron. Wiard's Woods (Box 9)
        - April 4, Gunther's Creek north of Saline, Mich. (Box 9)
        - May, Wilson Snipe. Roberts Pond (Box 9)
        - May, Cardinal at feeding station (Box 9)
        - May 3, Nests of great blue heron, Wiard's Woods (Box 9)
        - May 3, Nests of great blue heron, Wiard's Woods (Box 9)
        - May 3, Great blue heron and nests, Wiard's Woods (Box 9)
        - May 3, Nests of night heron about 75 ft. up, Ypsilanti (Box 9)
        - May 3, Nests of great blue heron, Wiard's Woods near Ypsilanti (Box 9)
        - May 5, Nests of great blue heron, Wiard's Woods (Box 9)
        - May 14, Columbia Lake (Box 9)
        - c. May 20, Cardinal at home feeding station, 96 Oakwood Ave., Ypsilanti (Box 9)
        - June 3, Shallows above ripples, Swallow nest pool (Box 9)
        - June 3, Sycamore Pool, Slaine River (Box 9)
        - June 6, Night herons nests and woods. Bay City heronry, swamp white oak trees (Box 9)
        - June 8, Brown thrasher's nest in barberry, NW corner of science garden (Box 9)
        - June 9, Killdeer, M.S.N.C. Athletic Field (Box 9)
        - June 9, Killdeer nest, baseball diamond, M.S.N.C. campus (Box 9)
        - June 9, Killdeer nest, baseball field., athletic grounds (Box 9)
        - June 9, Killdeer nesting place, M.S.N.C. athletic field (Box 9)
        - June 25, Baufuss [?] Lake, Hillsdale Co. just across the neck west of Cedar Island (Box 9)
    - September 1931-1934 (Box 10)
      - 1931
        - September 6, Fleming Creek. (Box 10)
        - September 6, Fleming Creek. Deep expansion[?] pool[?] (Box 10)
        - September 6, Fleming Creek. Just south of Dixboro. Showing pool and narrows (Box 10)
        - September 6, Fleming Creek down stream from bridge near mill at Geddes (Box 10)
        - September 6, Parker's Pond at Fleming Creek, just above mill (Box 10)
        - September 6, Garter snake swallowing a frog (R. clamitans) (Box 10)
        - September 13, Small Lake in marsh. Dexter Twp. (Box 10)
        - September 13, Swamp with Small Lake (Box 10)
        - September 13, Little Silver Lake looking SW from hill to east (Box 10)
      - 1932
        - March 27, Sand Lake, Lenawee Co., Michigan. (Box 10)
        - April 17, Pond and swamp on "Racer[?] dip" road (Box 10)
        - April 17, Pond and swamp on "Racer dip" road (Box 10)
        - April 17, Pond and swam-P on "Racer dip" road 1/2 mi. S. of Dixboro (Box 10)
        - April 24, Colony of Great blue heron's nests. Wiard's Woods, Ford's Place (Box 10)
        - April 24, Nests of Great blue heron. Wiard's Woods, Henry Ford's place (Box 10)
        - April 24, Great Blue Heron nests. Wiard's Woods, Ford's Place (Box 10)
        - April 24, Colony of black-crowned night heron nests (Box 10)
        - April 24, Black-crowned night herons. Nests at nesting habitat, Wiard's Woods on Ford's Place (Box 10)
        - April 24, Colony of great blue heron nests, Wiard's Woods on Ford's Place (Box 10)
        - April 29, Nest of mallard, Kellogg Bird Res. (Box 10)
        - April 29, Wild Canada geese at nest (Box 10)
        - April 29, Robins' nest, Kellogg Wild Life Sanctuary (Box 10)
        - April 29, Swans at Kellogg Wild Life Sanctuary (Box 10)
        - April 29, Black-crowned night herons, nests at nesting habitat. Wiard's Woods-Ford's place (Box 10)
        - May 8, Nest of ring-neck pheasant (Box 10)
        - May 10, Nest of ring-neck pheasant, Mullet Creek Valley (Box 10)
        - May 10, Nest of ring-neck pheasant, Mullet Creek Valley (Box 10)
        - May 8, Nest of ring-neck pheasant, Mullet Creek Valley (Box 10)
        - May 14, Saline River looking downstream from near water tower (Box 10)
        - May 31, Song sparrow's nest with two cowbird's eggs. Honey Creek Valley. Near Huron Drive (Box 10)
        - September 12, Bird planting 1 1/2 miles SW of Dixboro, Mich. (Box 10)
        - September 12, Dead Lake (Box 10)
        - September 25, First Sister Lake west of Ann Arbor (Box 10)
        - September 25, Henry Creek, near mouth, upstream from bridge (Box 10)
        - September 25, Marsh and pond at old mouth of Mallet Creek (Box 10)
        - October 2, Roadside west of Ann Arbor (Box 10)
        - October 9, Parker's Glen region. View from river slope (Box 10)
      - 1933
        - May 14, 1933 Pittsfield Ponds. Nesting habitat of Sora[?] and Pied-billed grebe (Box 10)
        - May 14, Nest of Sora[?] Rail, Pittsfield Pond (Box 10)
        - May 14 [?] Ground mole (Box 10)
        - June 24, Details of shrub zone. West side of Long Lake, Livingston Co., Mich. (Box 10)
        - June 24, Details of sedge zone. Long Lake, Livingston Co (Box 10)
        - June 24, Swamp shore. Long Lake, Livingston Co. (Box 10)
        - June 24, Long Lake, Livingston Co. (Box 10)
      - 1934
        - January 16, Skull of a rodent. L.P. Schultz (Box 10)
        - January 16, Skull of a rodent (Box 10)
        - January 16, Lower jaw of a rodent (Box 10)
        - January 16, Skull of a rodent. L. P. Schultz (Box 10)
        - January 16, Skull of a rodent. L. P. Schultz (Box 10)
        - June 15, Baltimore Oriole. Photo by Julian Strong, Azalia, Mich. (Box 10)
    - Personal, family, friends
      - T. L. Hankinson circa 1920 (Box 10)
      - T. L. Hankinson January 24, 1926 (Box 10)
      - T. L. Hankinson standing on head in water August 10, 1906 (Box 10)
      - T. L. Hankinson June 1929 (Box 10)
      - T. L. Hankinson house August 1914 (Box 10)
      - T. L. Hankinson house September 14, 1914 from SW (Box 10)
      - T. L. Hankinson, Nettie, Ag, Teddy June 29, 1908 (Box 10)
      - Nettie sewing in woods August 19, 1907 (Box 10)
      - Nettie on porch September 16, 1907 (Box 10)
      - Nettie Hankinson December 26, 1925 (Box 10)
      - Nettie and Katherine Adams June 1909 Charleston, Ill. (Box 10)
      - Janet Hankinson January 24, 1926 (Box 10)
      - Janet Hankinson December 1927 (Box 10)
      - Janet and Christmas tree December 25, 1925 (Box 10)
      - Janet riding by house May 2, 1921 (Box 10)
      - Uncle Herbert and Aunt Emma August 10, 1919 (Box 10)
      - Elizabeth Crowe and friends, Mitchell children and Nettie July 1909 Charleston, Ill. (Box 10)
      - Elizabeth Crowe and friends, Mitchell children and Nettie July 1909 (Box 10)
      - Miss Jackson, Miss Dickson at Urban Park, Charleston, Ill. March 26, 1907 (Box 10)
      - Miss Dickson picking flowers, Charleston, Ill. April 2, 1907 (Box 10)
      - Boy Scouts fishing August 1918 (Box 10)
      - Boy Scouts fishing August 1913 (Box 10)
      - Guest house and grounds, Palisades Park, N.Y. August 1918 (Box 10)
      - Guest house, Palisades Park, N.Y. August 1918 (Box 10)